chinawhisper.com 2015-06-26

# ReadyGraph

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the personal information (“Information”) collection and use procedures for the ReadyGraph powered-websites and social/mobile applications, and our website, located at www.ReadyGraph.com (collectively or separately, the “Service”), as well as any other social and mobile apps that ReadyGraph operates. This notice describes how such Information may be used or disclosed by ReadyGraph.  Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meanings set forth in the Terms of Service.   Please note that for data collected through ReadyGraph-powered sites, ReadyGraph may be acting as a data processor and service provider and collecting the data on behalf of our business clients (“Clients”). As part of the operation of the Service, we collect and may disclose information about you. By accepting and using the Service, you consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us. 

You should review this Privacy Policy frequently as ReadyGraph may update the Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised version of this Privacy Policy on or through the Service.  Your continued use of the Service after such notice constitutes your consent to the revised Privacy Policy. 

#### Information We Collect

In General. We may collect information that can identify you such as your name and email address ("personal information") and other information that does not identify you. We may collect this information through a ReadyGraph-powered website, ReadyGraph.com or a mobile or social (e.g. Facebook app) application. When you provide personal information through our website, the information may be sent to servers located in the United States and other countries around the world. 

Information you provide. We may collect and store any personal information you enter on our website or on a mobile application, or provide to us in some other manner. This includes but is not limited to identifying information, such as your name, address, email address and telephone number, and, if you transact business with us, financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information). You may also provide us information about your social connections, interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information such as your hometown or your username. 

Information from other sources. We may receive information about our users from third party social platforms, such as Facebook. When you access or use our website or mobile application through such a site, you allow us to access or collect information made available by the third party site in accordance with its privacy policy. This information may be available from your profile or account with such site or from cookies placed on your device by the third party platform. 

Information about others. We may collect and store personal information about other people that you provide to us, such as but not limited to their name, address and email address. If you use our website to send others (friends, relatives, colleagues, etc.) an invitation to Readygraph.com or a ReadyGraph-powered site or mobile or social app, we may store your personal information, and the personal information of each such recipient in order to process those requests or facilitate future activities. 

Use of cookies and other technologies to collect information. We use various technologies to collect information from your device and about your activities on the Service.

Information collected automatically. We automatically collect information from your browser or device when you visit any ReadyGraph-powered property or application. This information could include your IP address, device ID, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us (see "Cookies" below), and the referring website address. 

Cookies and Use of Cookie Data. When you visit our Service, we may assign your device one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the pages you visit, the time and date of your visits, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site. During your visits to other websites or applications where we advertise, we (or third parties) may use certain data collected on our site to show you ReadyGraph advertisements. Although you may not opt out of receiving online advertisements generally, you may control the collection of data on our site used for targeted ReadyGraph advertising during your visits to other websites. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on our Service. 

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's device for record keeping purposes. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A persistent cookie remains on your device for an extended period of time. Cookies on our site do not link to or store your personal information.

For example, when you sign in to the Service, we will record your user or member ID and the name associated with your user or member ID in the cookie file on your computer. We also may record your password in this cookie file, if you indicated that you would like your password saved for automatic sign-in. We may allow our service providers to serve cookies from our website or application to allow them to assist us in various activities, such as doing analysis and research on the effectiveness of our site, content and advertising.

You may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. (Click "Help" in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.) If you do so, some of the features and services of our website may not function properly.

We may allow third-parties, including advertising companies, analytics companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements or our website or mobile applications. They may collect information about where you, or others who are using your device, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver (such as click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, etc.), and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites or other data they have collected. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third-party's privacy policy. This policy covers the use of cookies by ReadyGraph only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Notwithstanding any other provision, we may also engage a data provider who may collect web log data from you (including IP address and information about your browser or operating system), or place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, that we may share with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these data provider cookies, please go to http://www.aboutads.info/choices. 

Other Technologies. We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our Service. We also may include web beacons in advertisements or email messages to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our website or application visitors to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities.

Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies which are stored on the user's device, web beacons are embedded invisibly on the web pages (or in email). 

Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. We also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website. Third parties may use anonymous information about your visits to our site and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Information collected by third-parties. We may allow service providers, advertising companies and ad networks, and other third parties to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies (www.networkadvertising.org).

In connection with the Service, we may collect Information in the following ways:

•           Through registration forms filled out by a user through the Service

•           Through Information provided by a user in connection with the purchase of products via the Service

•           Through the maintenance and analysis of Web server logs

•           Via communications between a user and us

•             Through our use of third-party databases from which user Information is extracted and   combined with Information obtained by us through the Service 

In connection with the Service, the types of Information about a user that we collect may include but is not limited to the following:

•           Name and/or Business Name

•           Postal address

•           E-mail address

•           Telephone number

•           Payment information (e.g. credit card numbers and billing addresses), if purchases or payments are made

•           Date of Birth/Age

•           Gender

•           Interests

•           Friends

•           Other technical information collected by the Service’s servers.

When you register for the Service you will be prompted to submit some personal information. We may retain in our files information you have requested be removed from our active databases for certain purposes, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce the Terms of Service. Moreover, such prior information may never be completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored ‘back up' systems. You should not expect that all of your Information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your request. 

#### How we use the information we collect

In General. We may use information that we collect about you to: 

deliver our products and services, and manage our business;

manage your account and provide you with customer support;

perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others; 

communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, or 3rd parties. You may obtain information and offers for products and services offered by Us as well as selected third parties. In order to accomplish the foregoing, We may provide the Information to trusted third parties, including but not limited to selected marketers 

develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our site and other sites, including providing our advertisements to you when you visit other sites;

perform ad tracking and website or mobile application analytics;

verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes; 

enforce or exercise any rights in our terms and conditions; and perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection 

In all circumstances, we may perform these functions directly or use a third party vendor to perform these functions on our behalf who will be obligated to use your personal information only to perform services for us. Also, if you access our Service from a third party social platform, such as Facebook, we may share non-personal information with that platform to the extent permitted by your agreement with it and its privacy settings. 

#### Control of Your Password/Authentication Mechanism

You are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password, including any fees or charges incurred based on such use. You must never share your login information with a third party. If you choose to share this information with a third party, you are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password by such third party. If you believe your password has been disclosed to third parties or otherwise compromised in any way you should immediately change your password. You should be sure to maintain the control and security of your device at all times to prevent unauthorized use.

We urge you to take steps to protect yourself as well. For example, select a neutral username that does not include your name or other personally identifiable information. To learn more about how to protect yourself online, we encourage you to visit government websites that address these issues.

#### Information you provide about yourself while using our service

We provide areas on our site where you can post information about yourself and others and communicate with others or upload content such as photographs. Such postings are governed by our Terms of Use. In addition, such postings may appear on other websites or when searches are executed on the subject of your posting. Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information.

#### A Special Note About Children

The Service is not intended for users under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly collect or retain Information in connection with the Service from children under the age of 13. If you are a parent and believe that your child has submitted information to ReadyGraph, please contact us immediately at support@readygraph.com. 

#### Visiting our websites from outside the United States

If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy.

#### Tracking Technologies

We also use tracking technologies to log information such as IP address, browser type and usage of the ReadyGraph website. The information collected in this manner is used for Service maintenance, development and potentially advertising. We may also employ "cookies" or similar technologies to provide additional functionality to our website and help us analyze the site usage more accurately. Some of the features on our website will only function if your browser is set to accept cookies. Thus, if you decline to accept cookies, certain features of our website may not operate properly. We reserve the right to use such tracking technologies for the purpose of marketing internal and third parties as well.

#### Email Policies

By default, we will send you periodic updates of various site information including welcome emails, site announcements, notifications and messages related to other ReadyGraph Services members and promotional email. You have full control regarding which of these emails you want to receive. To change your options, simply click "Unsubscribe" link from any email.

#### Push Notification Policies

We may send you periodic updates regarding the use of the Service through push notifications. These notifications may impact the data limits set by your provider. You may disable these notifications from the iOS “Settings” application on your device.

#### Our Use and Sharing of Information

ReadyGraph has functionality where we may collect some of your personal information through the Facebook Connect and the Graph API. Your data will be shared with us from Facebook or other social applications. We may use Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider to authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form and to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

For the aspects of our Service powered by Facebook applications we also use Facebook Permissions in order to give you the option to share personal information such as your activities and interests as well as the authorization to post information about your activity to your profile page on Facebook, other third party websites, and pages and emails powered by ReadyGraph.  Most personal information that may be collected is done so via an iframe or through a Facebook application on behalf of our client. Please refer to the privacy policy on the site/iframe where this data is collected.

If you post on a public forum, you should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our ReadyGraph, ReadyGraph-powered features, our blog or community forum, contact us as described below.  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information. 

We may use Information collected in connection with the Service in the following ways:

•           To provide requested information, products and services to users via the Service or through other online or offline channels

•           To improve the user experience with the Service

•           To enable users to obtain information and offers for products and Services offered by us as well as selected third parties.

In order to do the foregoing, we may provide the Information to third party service providers who help us bring you the services we offer, including but not limited to the operation of the Service, financial verification and payment services, communication services and fulfillment of orders, information verification, and third party marketing services.  We will use commercially reasonable efforts to limit use of the Information by such third parties to the provision of the services to us. These third parties may include the credit card companies and banking institutions used to process and support your transactions. By purchasing, or registering for, or making reservations for products or services of third parties offered on the Service, or by participating in programs offered on the Service that are administered by third parties and that require you to submit financial information in order to use them, you consent to our providing your financial information to those third parties. These third parties will be authorized to use your financial information in accordance with our contractual arrangements with such third parties and in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which we have no control, and you agree that we are not responsible or liable for any of their actions or omissions. 

Although we use industry-standard efforts to protect the Information we collect via the Service, we cannot guarantee that this information will not be accessed by the government or third parties in certain circumstances. We may be required by law to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties. You authorize us to report consumer transaction data to third parties for fraud prevention services. In addition, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications and other services may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from the Service. Accordingly, you should not expect that your Information or private communications will remain private in all circumstances. 

We use information in the data files we maintain about you, and the other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Service to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce the Terms of Use. We may review the data of multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes. 

We may share data collected via the Service, including Information about you, with our parent, affiliates, subsidiaries, or third parties. It is possible that we could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such merger or acquisition occur, we reserve the right to share some or all of your Information with the merger partner or acquiring party. 

We may also share your information with third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our site and on websites or applications of third parties, and to analyze and report on advertising you see. We may combine information we collect with additional information collected from other sources. We also may share information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis or other business purposes. 

In addition, we reserve the right to share your information in the following scenarios:

In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.

When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce our website terms and conditions or other agreements or policies.

#### Fraud

Without limiting any other remedies, ReadyGraph may suspend or terminate your account if it suspects that you (by conviction, settlement, insurance or escrow investigation, or otherwise) have engaged in fraudulent activity in connection with the ReadyGraph service.

#### Restricted Activities

Your use of the ReadyGraph service shall not: (a) be false, inaccurate or misleading; (b) be fraudulent or involve the sale of illegal services or items; (c) infringe any third party’s copyright, patent, trademark, trade secret or other proprietary rights or rights of publicity or privacy; (d) violate any applicable law, statute, professional code of conduct, ordinance or regulation (including, but not limited to restrictions on sharing of fees, restrictions on giving referral fees, consumer protection, unfair competition, antidiscrimination or false advertising); (e) be defamatory, trade libelous, unlawfully threatening or unlawfully harassing; (f) be obscene or contain child pornography; (g) contain any viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time bombs, cancelbots, easter eggs or other computer programming routines that may damage, detrimentally interfere with, surreptitiously intercept or expropriate any system, data or personal information; (h) create liability for us or cause us to lose (in whole or in part) the services of our ISPs or other suppliers; and (i) link directly or indirectly to or include descriptions of goods or services that are prohibited under this Agreement or ones that you do not have a right to link to or include.

#### License

Solely to enable ReadyGraph to use the information you supply us with, so that we are not violating any rights you might have in that information, you agree to grant us a non-exclusive, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, sub-licensable (through multiple tiers) right to exercise the copyright, publicity, and database rights (but no other rights) you have in your information, in any media now known or not currently known, with respect to your information. ReadyGraph will only use your information in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

#### Third Party Use of Information

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your Information to other parties, whether via the Service or on sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. We do not control the privacy policies of any third parties so you should investigate their policies before you disclose your Information to them.

Information you submit will be used to respond to your request. We may also use your information for other legitimate business purposes, including sending you notices about ReadyGraph, its products and services, or asking for your input and feedback on our products and services.

#### Contact Information

App Uprising, Inc. 20 Jay St. Brooklyn, NY 11201 support@readygraph.com +1 (862) 205-4769

Last Updated: 01/2/2014
